{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873974740","data":{"timestamp":" 946873974740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873987748","data":{"timestamp":" 946873987747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873987982","data":{"timestamp":" 946873987981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873988960","data":{"timestamp":" 946873988959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873990242","data":{"timestamp":" 946873990241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873993191","data":{"timestamp":" 946873993190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873994045","data":{"timestamp":" 946873994044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873994370","data":{"timestamp":" 946873994369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873995614","data":{"timestamp":" 946873995613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873999191","data":{"timestamp":" 946873999191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874000176","data":{"timestamp":" 946874000176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874000435","data":{"timestamp":" 946874000434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874001391","data":{"timestamp":" 946874001391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874004278","data":{"timestamp":" 946874004278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874005319","data":{"timestamp":" 946874005318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874005799","data":{"timestamp":" 946874005798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874010359","data":{"timestamp":" 946874010359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874010420","data":{"timestamp":" 946874010420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4f73a525-71fb-4a09-a7ec-6be64a5e276b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874023419","data":{"timestamp":" 946874023418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874025614","data":{"timestamp":" 946874025614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874028242","data":{"timestamp":" 946874028242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874029837","data":{"timestamp":" 946874029837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874031785","data":{"timestamp":" 946874031785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874033739","data":{"timestamp":" 946874033739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874036408","data":{"timestamp":" 946874036407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874038044","data":{"timestamp":" 946874038043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874039240","data":{"timestamp":" 946874039240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" NINAPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874039846","data":{"timestamp":" 946874039846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874040084","data":{"timestamp":" 946874040084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874040543","data":{"timestamp":" 946874040542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874041260","data":{"timestamp":" 946874041260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874042206","data":{"timestamp":" 946874042206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874044823","data":{"timestamp":" 946874044823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874047192","data":{"timestamp":" 946874047191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874049200","data":{"timestamp":" 946874049200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874051319","data":{"timestamp":" 946874051319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874054127","data":{"timestamp":" 946874054127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874056160","data":{"timestamp":" 946874056159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874057752","data":{"timestamp":" 946874057752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874058275","data":{"timestamp":" 946874058275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874059318","data":{"timestamp":" 946874059318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874059922","data":{"timestamp":" 946874059922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874060559","data":{"timestamp":" 946874060559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874061607","data":{"timestamp":" 946874061606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874064360","data":{"timestamp":" 946874064359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874066620","data":{"timestamp":" 946874066620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874068508","data":{"timestamp":" 946874068507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874070537","data":{"timestamp":" 946874070537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874072287","data":{"timestamp":" 946874072287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874073160","data":{"timestamp":" 946874073160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874073624","data":{"timestamp":" 946874073623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874074636","data":{"timestamp":" 946874074635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874081765","data":{"timestamp":" 946874081765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874085508","data":{"timestamp":" 946874085508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874087242","data":{"timestamp":" 946874087242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874088239","data":{"timestamp":" 946874088239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874092828","data":{"timestamp":" 946874092827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874094929","data":{"timestamp":" 946874094929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874097022","data":{"timestamp":" 946874097022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874099479","data":{"timestamp":" 946874099479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874101461","data":{"timestamp":" 946874101460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874103182","data":{"timestamp":" 946874103182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874105205","data":{"timestamp":" 946874105205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874107192","data":{"timestamp":" 946874107192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874109076","data":{"timestamp":" 946874109076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874109569","data":{"timestamp":" 946874109569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874109676","data":{"timestamp":" 946874109676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874110392","data":{"timestamp":" 946874110391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874111369","data":{"timestamp":" 946874111369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874112048","data":{"timestamp":" 946874112047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874112888","data":{"timestamp":" 946874112888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874113474","data":{"timestamp":" 946874113473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874117180","data":{"timestamp":" 946874117180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874119645","data":{"timestamp":" 946874119644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874121132","data":{"timestamp":" 946874121131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874123174","data":{"timestamp":" 946874123173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874125850","data":{"timestamp":" 946874125850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874129058","data":{"timestamp":" 946874129058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874131186","data":{"timestamp":" 946874131186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874133017","data":{"timestamp":" 946874133017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874133476","data":{"timestamp":" 946874133476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874133948","data":{"timestamp":" 946874133947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874134722","data":{"timestamp":" 946874134722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874135298","data":{"timestamp":" 946874135298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874135988","data":{"timestamp":" 946874135988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874136593","data":{"timestamp":" 946874136593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" KUYANYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874139279","data":{"timestamp":" 946874139279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874142187","data":{"timestamp":" 946874142186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874144369","data":{"timestamp":" 946874144368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874146596","data":{"timestamp":" 946874146596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874148371","data":{"timestamp":" 946874148371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874149245","data":{"timestamp":" 946874149245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874149719","data":{"timestamp":" 946874149719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874150731","data":{"timestamp":" 946874150730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874154377","data":{"timestamp":" 946874154377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874156808","data":{"timestamp":" 946874156808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874158546","data":{"timestamp":" 946874158546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874159544","data":{"timestamp":" 946874159543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874164452","data":{"timestamp":" 946874164451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874166009","data":{"timestamp":" 946874166009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874168053","data":{"timestamp":" 946874168053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874171058","data":{"timestamp":" 946874171058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874173383","data":{"timestamp":" 946874173383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874174868","data":{"timestamp":" 946874174867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874176880","data":{"timestamp":" 946874176879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874179552","data":{"timestamp":" 946874179551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874181349","data":{"timestamp":" 946874181349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874183220","data":{"timestamp":" 946874183220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874185382","data":{"timestamp":" 946874185382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" MAPAZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874185455","data":{"timestamp":" 946874185455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874186420","data":{"timestamp":" 946874186420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" MADIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874188147","data":{"timestamp":" 946874188146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" YANAPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874188751","data":{"timestamp":" 946874188751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874189195","data":{"timestamp":" 946874189194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874189728","data":{"timestamp":" 946874189728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874191427","data":{"timestamp":" 946874191427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" YANANIPANGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874191855","data":{"timestamp":" 946874191855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874192402","data":{"timestamp":" 946874192402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874196288","data":{"timestamp":" 946874196288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874198505","data":{"timestamp":" 946874198505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874203467","data":{"timestamp":" 946874203466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874205455","data":{"timestamp":" 946874205455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874207272","data":{"timestamp":" 946874207272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874208155","data":{"timestamp":" 946874208155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874208658","data":{"timestamp":" 946874208658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874209711","data":{"timestamp":" 946874209711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874227388","data":{"timestamp":" 946874227388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874232041","data":{"timestamp":" 946874232041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874233805","data":{"timestamp":" 946874233804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874234802","data":{"timestamp":" 946874234802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874238006","data":{"timestamp":" 946874238006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874239505","data":{"timestamp":" 946874239504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874241538","data":{"timestamp":" 946874241537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874243333","data":{"timestamp":" 946874243333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874243587","data":{"timestamp":" 946874243587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874244560","data":{"timestamp":" 946874244560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874248802","data":{"timestamp":" 946874248802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874251512","data":{"timestamp":" 946874251512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874253937","data":{"timestamp":" 946874253937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874255945","data":{"timestamp":" 946874255945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874258311","data":{"timestamp":" 946874258311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874260175","data":{"timestamp":" 946874260175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874260974","data":{"timestamp":" 946874260973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874262157","data":{"timestamp":" 946874262157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" YANASONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874262751","data":{"timestamp":" 946874262751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874263215","data":{"timestamp":" 946874263215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874266722","data":{"timestamp":" 946874266722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874268954","data":{"timestamp":" 946874268954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874271347","data":{"timestamp":" 946874271347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874273439","data":{"timestamp":" 946874273439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874275203","data":{"timestamp":" 946874275203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874276076","data":{"timestamp":" 946874276076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874276539","data":{"timestamp":" 946874276539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874277542","data":{"timestamp":" 946874277542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874352968","data":{"timestamp":" 946874352968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874450165","data":{"timestamp":" 946874450165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874451874","data":{"timestamp":" 946874451874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874452857","data":{"timestamp":" 946874452857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874457115","data":{"timestamp":" 946874457114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874459486","data":{"timestamp":" 946874459485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874461205","data":{"timestamp":" 946874461205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874465348","data":{"timestamp":" 946874465348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874468065","data":{"timestamp":" 946874468065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874470049","data":{"timestamp":" 946874470048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874471463","data":{"timestamp":" 946874471462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874471945","data":{"timestamp":" 946874471945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874472668","data":{"timestamp":" 946874472668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874473717","data":{"timestamp":" 946874473716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" KUTETEMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874478209","data":{"timestamp":" 946874478209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874480944","data":{"timestamp":" 946874480944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874482524","data":{"timestamp":" 946874482523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874484583","data":{"timestamp":" 946874484582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874486802","data":{"timestamp":" 946874486802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874488144","data":{"timestamp":" 946874488144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" YANAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874488498","data":{"timestamp":" 946874488497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874489069","data":{"timestamp":" 946874489069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874494222","data":{"timestamp":" 946874494222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874496910","data":{"timestamp":" 946874496910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874501303","data":{"timestamp":" 946874501302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874503098","data":{"timestamp":" 946874503097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874504081","data":{"timestamp":" 946874504081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874504579","data":{"timestamp":" 946874504578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874507370","data":{"timestamp":" 946874507370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874511126","data":{"timestamp":" 946874511126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874513073","data":{"timestamp":" 946874513072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874514790","data":{"timestamp":" 946874514790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874515774","data":{"timestamp":" 946874515774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874519673","data":{"timestamp":" 946874519673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874524041","data":{"timestamp":" 946874524041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874527998","data":{"timestamp":" 946874527997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874532435","data":{"timestamp":" 946874532434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874535960","data":{"timestamp":" 946874535959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874540341","data":{"timestamp":" 946874540340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874544383","data":{"timestamp":" 946874544383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874548845","data":{"timestamp":" 946874548845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874552127","data":{"timestamp":" 946874552127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874555914","data":{"timestamp":" 946874555914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874559978","data":{"timestamp":" 946874559978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874561745","data":{"timestamp":" 946874561745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874561927","data":{"timestamp":" 946874561927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874562651","data":{"timestamp":" 946874562651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874563991","data":{"timestamp":" 946874563990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUNACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874565304","data":{"timestamp":" 946874565304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874566208","data":{"timestamp":" 946874566208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874567245","data":{"timestamp":" 946874567244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" KUNUSIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874568522","data":{"timestamp":" 946874568522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874569228","data":{"timestamp":" 946874569228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" AMBAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874569742","data":{"timestamp":" 946874569742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874570956","data":{"timestamp":" 946874570956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ANATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874576389","data":{"timestamp":" 946874576389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874580947","data":{"timestamp":" 946874580946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874584069","data":{"timestamp":" 946874584069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874588313","data":{"timestamp":" 946874588312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874590118","data":{"timestamp":" 946874590118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874591002","data":{"timestamp":" 946874591002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874591514","data":{"timestamp":" 946874591513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874592578","data":{"timestamp":" 946874592578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874595578","data":{"timestamp":" 946874595578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874600436","data":{"timestamp":" 946874600436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874602172","data":{"timestamp":" 946874602171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874603154","data":{"timestamp":" 946874603154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874607920","data":{"timestamp":" 946874607920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874611236","data":{"timestamp":" 946874611236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874615693","data":{"timestamp":" 946874615693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874618896","data":{"timestamp":" 946874618896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874624692","data":{"timestamp":" 946874624692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874628665","data":{"timestamp":" 946874628665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874632453","data":{"timestamp":" 946874632452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874634501","data":{"timestamp":" 946874634501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" BILAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874634994","data":{"timestamp":" 946874634994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874635981","data":{"timestamp":" 946874635981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874637054","data":{"timestamp":" 946874637054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" INAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874637517","data":{"timestamp":" 946874637517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874637711","data":{"timestamp":" 946874637711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874638523","data":{"timestamp":" 946874638523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874643893","data":{"timestamp":" 946874643893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874646636","data":{"timestamp":" 946874646635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874651748","data":{"timestamp":" 946874651747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874655817","data":{"timestamp":" 946874655817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874657676","data":{"timestamp":" 946874657676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874658259","data":{"timestamp":" 946874658259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" MUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874659232","data":{"timestamp":" 946874659232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874659876","data":{"timestamp":" 946874659876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874664382","data":{"timestamp":" 946874664382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874668103","data":{"timestamp":" 946874668103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874671800","data":{"timestamp":" 946874671800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874675375","data":{"timestamp":" 946874675375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874677151","data":{"timestamp":" 946874677151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874677995","data":{"timestamp":" 946874677995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874678762","data":{"timestamp":" 946874678761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" UKATILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874679184","data":{"timestamp":" 946874679183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874683602","data":{"timestamp":" 946874683602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874687587","data":{"timestamp":" 946874687587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874691404","data":{"timestamp":" 946874691404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874695148","data":{"timestamp":" 946874695148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874697060","data":{"timestamp":" 946874697059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874698532","data":{"timestamp":" 946874698532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874699045","data":{"timestamp":" 946874699045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874700048","data":{"timestamp":" 946874700048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874700311","data":{"timestamp":" 946874700311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874701204","data":{"timestamp":" 946874701204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874705635","data":{"timestamp":" 946874705635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874709307","data":{"timestamp":" 946874709306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874711189","data":{"timestamp":" 946874711188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" FIRIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874712332","data":{"timestamp":" 946874712332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" INAPULIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874716314","data":{"timestamp":" 946874716314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874718516","data":{"timestamp":" 946874718516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874720557","data":{"timestamp":" 946874720556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874724171","data":{"timestamp":" 946874724170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874725722","data":{"timestamp":" 946874725722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874725885","data":{"timestamp":" 946874725885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874726508","data":{"timestamp":" 946874726508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874727457","data":{"timestamp":" 946874727457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" LINAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874732276","data":{"timestamp":" 946874732276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874735984","data":{"timestamp":" 946874735984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874739584","data":{"timestamp":" 946874739584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874743095","data":{"timestamp":" 946874743095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874745723","data":{"timestamp":" 946874745723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874747878","data":{"timestamp":" 946874747878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" SILIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874748761","data":{"timestamp":" 946874748761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874749344","data":{"timestamp":" 946874749344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874749718","data":{"timestamp":" 946874749717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874750251","data":{"timestamp":" 946874750250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874753710","data":{"timestamp":" 946874753709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874757737","data":{"timestamp":" 946874757737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874761516","data":{"timestamp":" 946874761516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874765453","data":{"timestamp":" 946874765453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874767204","data":{"timestamp":" 946874767203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874768077","data":{"timestamp":" 946874768077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874768540","data":{"timestamp":" 946874768540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874769556","data":{"timestamp":" 946874769556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874773356","data":{"timestamp":" 946874773355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874776057","data":{"timestamp":" 946874776057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874777779","data":{"timestamp":" 946874777779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874778762","data":{"timestamp":" 946874778762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874785682","data":{"timestamp":" 946874785682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874788280","data":{"timestamp":" 946874788279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" HAIONEKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874792271","data":{"timestamp":" 946874792271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874794617","data":{"timestamp":" 946874794617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" HAISIKIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874796419","data":{"timestamp":" 946874796419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" START_INAFANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874804475","data":{"timestamp":" 946874804475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874807931","data":{"timestamp":" 946874807931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874811572","data":{"timestamp":" 946874811572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874814638","data":{"timestamp":" 946874814638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874818929","data":{"timestamp":" 946874818928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874820882","data":{"timestamp":" 946874820882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" INAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874821266","data":{"timestamp":" 946874821266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874821860","data":{"timestamp":" 946874821860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874822617","data":{"timestamp":" 946874822617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874823072","data":{"timestamp":" 946874823071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874826807","data":{"timestamp":" 946874826806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874829394","data":{"timestamp":" 946874829393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874832987","data":{"timestamp":" 946874832986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874834922","data":{"timestamp":" 946874834922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874835346","data":{"timestamp":" 946874835346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874836150","data":{"timestamp":" 946874836149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874840636","data":{"timestamp":" 946874840635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874844575","data":{"timestamp":" 946874844575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874846340","data":{"timestamp":" 946874846340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874847084","data":{"timestamp":" 946874847084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874852488","data":{"timestamp":" 946874852487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874856759","data":{"timestamp":" 946874856759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874858251","data":{"timestamp":" 946874858251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874858994","data":{"timestamp":" 946874858994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874880378","data":{"timestamp":" 946874880377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874880452","data":{"timestamp":" 946874880451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874886052","data":{"timestamp":" 946874886052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" fc16764b-329b-415d-84d6-37fcca466f87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874897892","data":{"timestamp":" 946874897892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874898776","data":{"timestamp":" 946874898776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874899829","data":{"timestamp":" 946874899829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874900092","data":{"timestamp":" 946874900092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874900605","data":{"timestamp":" 946874900605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874901451","data":{"timestamp":" 946874901450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874903902","data":{"timestamp":" 946874903902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874905940","data":{"timestamp":" 946874905940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874907772","data":{"timestamp":" 946874907772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874909499","data":{"timestamp":" 946874909499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874911226","data":{"timestamp":" 946874911226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874913911","data":{"timestamp":" 946874913911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874915764","data":{"timestamp":" 946874915764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874916335","data":{"timestamp":" 946874916334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874917159","data":{"timestamp":" 946874917159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874917622","data":{"timestamp":" 946874917622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874918295","data":{"timestamp":" 946874918295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874924266","data":{"timestamp":" 946874924266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874925948","data":{"timestamp":" 946874925948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874928258","data":{"timestamp":" 946874928258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874929902","data":{"timestamp":" 946874929901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874931795","data":{"timestamp":" 946874931795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874933910","data":{"timestamp":" 946874933910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874934783","data":{"timestamp":" 946874934783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874935567","data":{"timestamp":" 946874935566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874936190","data":{"timestamp":" 946874936190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874936863","data":{"timestamp":" 946874936863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874939528","data":{"timestamp":" 946874939527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874941738","data":{"timestamp":" 946874941738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874944044","data":{"timestamp":" 946874944044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874946243","data":{"timestamp":" 946874946243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874948851","data":{"timestamp":" 946874948851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874951099","data":{"timestamp":" 946874951099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874951803","data":{"timestamp":" 946874951803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874952792","data":{"timestamp":" 946874952791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874953858","data":{"timestamp":" 946874953857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" ALIYEISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874954513","data":{"timestamp":" 946874954512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874955150","data":{"timestamp":" 946874955150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874956378","data":{"timestamp":" 946874956377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874956972","data":{"timestamp":" 946874956972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874957126","data":{"timestamp":" 946874957126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874957671","data":{"timestamp":" 946874957671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874958895","data":{"timestamp":" 946874958894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874960227","data":{"timestamp":" 946874960227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874960758","data":{"timestamp":" 946874960757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874961102","data":{"timestamp":" 946874961101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874962073","data":{"timestamp":" 946874962072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874963286","data":{"timestamp":" 946874963286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874963941","data":{"timestamp":" 946874963941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874964836","data":{"timestamp":" 946874964836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEJAA"," userResponse":" UMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874965140","data":{"timestamp":" 946874965139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANG"," userResponse":" MANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874965667","data":{"timestamp":" 946874965667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMUNG"," userResponse":" AMUNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874966241","data":{"timestamp":" 946874966241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMU"," userResponse":" AMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874967078","data":{"timestamp":" 946874967077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874967712","data":{"timestamp":" 946874967712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874969128","data":{"timestamp":" 946874969127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIKULOWESHA"," userResponse":" IKIKULOWESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874971566","data":{"timestamp":" 946874971566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874972909","data":{"timestamp":" 946874972909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874974710","data":{"timestamp":" 946874974710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874976942","data":{"timestamp":" 946874976942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874979243","data":{"timestamp":" 946874979243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874981225","data":{"timestamp":" 946874981225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874983411","data":{"timestamp":" 946874983411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874985227","data":{"timestamp":" 946874985227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874986848","data":{"timestamp":" 946874986848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874988947","data":{"timestamp":" 946874988947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874990523","data":{"timestamp":" 946874990523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874992655","data":{"timestamp":" 946874992655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874994865","data":{"timestamp":" 946874994865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874996562","data":{"timestamp":" 946874996562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946874998800","data":{"timestamp":" 946874998800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875001064","data":{"timestamp":" 946875001064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875003027","data":{"timestamp":" 946875003027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875004856","data":{"timestamp":" 946875004856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875007037","data":{"timestamp":" 946875007037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875008832","data":{"timestamp":" 946875008831"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMUNG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875010658","data":{"timestamp":" 946875010658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875012326","data":{"timestamp":" 946875012326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875014134","data":{"timestamp":" 946875014134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875016821","data":{"timestamp":" 946875016821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIKULOWESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875019294","data":{"timestamp":" 946875019293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875020188","data":{"timestamp":" 946875020187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875021563","data":{"timestamp":" 946875021563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNALALA"," userResponse":" TUNALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875023062","data":{"timestamp":" 946875023061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875024366","data":{"timestamp":" 946875024366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875024680","data":{"timestamp":" 946875024680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875025862","data":{"timestamp":" 946875025861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATEMI"," userResponse":" WATEMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875028789","data":{"timestamp":" 946875028789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875030698","data":{"timestamp":" 946875030697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875033303","data":{"timestamp":" 946875033303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875035272","data":{"timestamp":" 946875035272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875038712","data":{"timestamp":" 946875038712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875040654","data":{"timestamp":" 946875040653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875042627","data":{"timestamp":" 946875042626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATEMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875045005","data":{"timestamp":" 946875045004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875045970","data":{"timestamp":" 946875045969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875047099","data":{"timestamp":" 946875047098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875047646","data":{"timestamp":" 946875047646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875051477","data":{"timestamp":" 946875051476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875053723","data":{"timestamp":" 946875053723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875056090","data":{"timestamp":" 946875056090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875060211","data":{"timestamp":" 946875060210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875062603","data":{"timestamp":" 946875062603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFADHALI"," userResponse":" AFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875063763","data":{"timestamp":" 946875063762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNITEMBELEE"," userResponse":" UNITEMBELEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875064613","data":{"timestamp":" 946875064611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875065201","data":{"timestamp":" 946875065200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875066405","data":{"timestamp":" 946875066405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONE"," userResponse":" UKAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875067734","data":{"timestamp":" 946875067734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAHARI"," userResponse":" FAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875069246","data":{"timestamp":" 946875069245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPO"," userResponse":" ILIYOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875069869","data":{"timestamp":" 946875069869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875070951","data":{"timestamp":" 946875070950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875072370","data":{"timestamp":" 946875072369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875072950","data":{"timestamp":" 946875072950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875073132","data":{"timestamp":" 946875073131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875073781","data":{"timestamp":" 946875073781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875076566","data":{"timestamp":" 946875076566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875078642","data":{"timestamp":" 946875078642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNITEMBELEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875080283","data":{"timestamp":" 946875080282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875081580","data":{"timestamp":" 946875081580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875083826","data":{"timestamp":" 946875083825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875086351","data":{"timestamp":" 946875086351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAHARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875088696","data":{"timestamp":" 946875088696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875090592","data":{"timestamp":" 946875090592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875093062","data":{"timestamp":" 946875093062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875096008","data":{"timestamp":" 946875096008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875098243","data":{"timestamp":" 946875098243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875100378","data":{"timestamp":" 946875100378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875102383","data":{"timestamp":" 946875102383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875104205","data":{"timestamp":" 946875104204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875104792","data":{"timestamp":" 946875104792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875105476","data":{"timestamp":" 946875105475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875106296","data":{"timestamp":" 946875106295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875107503","data":{"timestamp":" 946875107502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875108038","data":{"timestamp":" 946875108038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875108214","data":{"timestamp":" 946875108213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875108830","data":{"timestamp":" 946875108830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875112099","data":{"timestamp":" 946875112098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875113896","data":{"timestamp":" 946875113896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875115581","data":{"timestamp":" 946875115581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875117675","data":{"timestamp":" 946875117675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875119536","data":{"timestamp":" 946875119536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875121154","data":{"timestamp":" 946875121153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875122776","data":{"timestamp":" 946875122776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875124898","data":{"timestamp":" 946875124897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875126677","data":{"timestamp":" 946875126677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875127445","data":{"timestamp":" 946875127444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875127967","data":{"timestamp":" 946875127966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875128799","data":{"timestamp":" 946875128799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRIJA"," userResponse":" MRIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875130034","data":{"timestamp":" 946875130033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" UNAOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875131111","data":{"timestamp":" 946875131111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINWAJI"," userResponse":" KINWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875133872","data":{"timestamp":" 946875133872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875136050","data":{"timestamp":" 946875136050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875137853","data":{"timestamp":" 946875137852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875139681","data":{"timestamp":" 946875139681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRIJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875141879","data":{"timestamp":" 946875141879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875144052","data":{"timestamp":" 946875144052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINWAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875146576","data":{"timestamp":" 946875146576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875147431","data":{"timestamp":" 946875147430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875147896","data":{"timestamp":" 946875147896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875148774","data":{"timestamp":" 946875148773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875149308","data":{"timestamp":" 946875149308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875150726","data":{"timestamp":" 946875150726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875152046","data":{"timestamp":" 946875152045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJABU"," userResponse":" AJABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875153294","data":{"timestamp":" 946875153293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFOKA"," userResponse":" AKIFOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875154133","data":{"timestamp":" 946875154133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUSI"," userResponse":" MATUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875155497","data":{"timestamp":" 946875155497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875155961","data":{"timestamp":" 946875155961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875156813","data":{"timestamp":" 946875156812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOKULA"," userResponse":" WANAOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875157341","data":{"timestamp":" 946875157340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875157838","data":{"timestamp":" 946875157837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875159416","data":{"timestamp":" 946875159415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAONA"," userResponse":" WATAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875159761","data":{"timestamp":" 946875159761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875160373","data":{"timestamp":" 946875160372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEMA"," userResponse":" MTEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875161254","data":{"timestamp":" 946875161253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875164223","data":{"timestamp":" 946875164223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875165942","data":{"timestamp":" 946875165941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875167664","data":{"timestamp":" 946875167663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875169379","data":{"timestamp":" 946875169379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875171401","data":{"timestamp":" 946875171401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875173696","data":{"timestamp":" 946875173696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875176686","data":{"timestamp":" 946875176685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875179058","data":{"timestamp":" 946875179058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875181207","data":{"timestamp":" 946875181207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875183259","data":{"timestamp":" 946875183259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875185239","data":{"timestamp":" 946875185237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875187511","data":{"timestamp":" 946875187510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875189507","data":{"timestamp":" 946875189507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875191646","data":{"timestamp":" 946875191645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875193556","data":{"timestamp":" 946875193556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875196313","data":{"timestamp":" 946875196313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875198960","data":{"timestamp":" 946875198960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875201295","data":{"timestamp":" 946875201295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875203229","data":{"timestamp":" 946875203228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875204690","data":{"timestamp":" 946875204689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWATEGEA"," userResponse":" AKAWATEGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875205351","data":{"timestamp":" 946875205351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875206461","data":{"timestamp":" 946875206460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ULIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875207697","data":{"timestamp":" 946875207696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875210414","data":{"timestamp":" 946875210414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875212768","data":{"timestamp":" 946875212768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWATEGEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875214391","data":{"timestamp":" 946875214391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875216504","data":{"timestamp":" 946875216504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIYOJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875218336","data":{"timestamp":" 946875218335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875220651","data":{"timestamp":" 946875220650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875221617","data":{"timestamp":" 946875221617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875222432","data":{"timestamp":" 946875222431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875222865","data":{"timestamp":" 946875222865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875223658","data":{"timestamp":" 946875223658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875224540","data":{"timestamp":" 946875224540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOMO"," userResponse":" VILIVYOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875227290","data":{"timestamp":" 946875227290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875229653","data":{"timestamp":" 946875229653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875231599","data":{"timestamp":" 946875231599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875233327","data":{"timestamp":" 946875233326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875235213","data":{"timestamp":" 946875235213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875237136","data":{"timestamp":" 946875237136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875239329","data":{"timestamp":" 946875239328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875240394","data":{"timestamp":" 946875240394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEKA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875241248","data":{"timestamp":" 946875241248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" CHU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875247047","data":{"timestamp":" 946875247047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875249324","data":{"timestamp":" 946875249324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875251003","data":{"timestamp":" 946875251003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875254192","data":{"timestamp":" 946875254191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875254898","data":{"timestamp":" 946875254897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875255753","data":{"timestamp":" 946875255752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875255933","data":{"timestamp":" 946875255932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875256447","data":{"timestamp":" 946875256446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875257445","data":{"timestamp":" 946875257444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875258756","data":{"timestamp":" 946875258755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" WACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875259503","data":{"timestamp":" 946875259503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONJE"," userResponse":" NIONJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875260306","data":{"timestamp":" 946875260306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875264376","data":{"timestamp":" 946875264375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875266300","data":{"timestamp":" 946875266300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875268340","data":{"timestamp":" 946875268340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875270510","data":{"timestamp":" 946875270510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875272563","data":{"timestamp":" 946875272562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875274845","data":{"timestamp":" 946875274845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875276505","data":{"timestamp":" 946875276505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875278465","data":{"timestamp":" 946875278464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875280502","data":{"timestamp":" 946875280502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875282585","data":{"timestamp":" 946875282584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAZAMA"," userResponse":" TAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875283193","data":{"timestamp":" 946875283192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875283860","data":{"timestamp":" 946875283859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875284818","data":{"timestamp":" 946875284818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAVYOKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAVYOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875285291","data":{"timestamp":" 946875285291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875287875","data":{"timestamp":" 946875287875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAZAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875289624","data":{"timestamp":" 946875289624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875291566","data":{"timestamp":" 946875291566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875293807","data":{"timestamp":" 946875293807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAVYOKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875295736","data":{"timestamp":" 946875295736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875298215","data":{"timestamp":" 946875298215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875298808","data":{"timestamp":" 946875298808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875299370","data":{"timestamp":" 946875299370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875300090","data":{"timestamp":" 946875300088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAPATA"," userResponse":" HAJAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875300737","data":{"timestamp":" 946875300736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUSA"," userResponse":" KUGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875301995","data":{"timestamp":" 946875301994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875303165","data":{"timestamp":" 946875303165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875304660","data":{"timestamp":" 946875304659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMNASA"," userResponse":" UKAMNASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875305276","data":{"timestamp":" 946875305275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875308436","data":{"timestamp":" 946875308435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875310666","data":{"timestamp":" 946875310665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875312778","data":{"timestamp":" 946875312778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875315317","data":{"timestamp":" 946875315317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875317238","data":{"timestamp":" 946875317238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUGUSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875319056","data":{"timestamp":" 946875319056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875320759","data":{"timestamp":" 946875320758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875322631","data":{"timestamp":" 946875322631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAMNASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875324606","data":{"timestamp":" 946875324606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875326607","data":{"timestamp":" 946875326607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875327251","data":{"timestamp":" 946875327251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875328945","data":{"timestamp":" 946875328944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKABUBUJIKA"," userResponse":" YAKABUBUJIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875329479","data":{"timestamp":" 946875329478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875330634","data":{"timestamp":" 946875330633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILINGANYI"," userResponse":" MBILINGANYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875333375","data":{"timestamp":" 946875333375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875335022","data":{"timestamp":" 946875335022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875337239","data":{"timestamp":" 946875337239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKABUBUJIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875338919","data":{"timestamp":" 946875338919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875341122","data":{"timestamp":" 946875341122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Macho yake yakabubujika kama mbilinganyi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILINGANYI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875343413","data":{"timestamp":" 946875343413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875343608","data":{"timestamp":" 946875343608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875344163","data":{"timestamp":" 946875344162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875345601","data":{"timestamp":" 946875345601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMTAZAMA"," userResponse":" AKAMTAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875347251","data":{"timestamp":" 946875347250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEDUWAA"," userResponse":" AMEDUWAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875350260","data":{"timestamp":" 946875350260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875352087","data":{"timestamp":" 946875352087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875353875","data":{"timestamp":" 946875353875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875356447","data":{"timestamp":" 946875356447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMTAZAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875359240","data":{"timestamp":" 946875359240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wa nyika akamtazama ameduwaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEDUWAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875361276","data":{"timestamp":" 946875361276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875362028","data":{"timestamp":" 946875362027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875365712","data":{"timestamp":" 946875365711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" START_AMEDUWAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875368593","data":{"timestamp":" 946875368593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875370315","data":{"timestamp":" 946875370315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875371762","data":{"timestamp":" 946875371762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEEE"," userResponse":" HEEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875373659","data":{"timestamp":" 946875373659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875374144","data":{"timestamp":" 946875374143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875374839","data":{"timestamp":" 946875374838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMU"," userResponse":" KITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875375183","data":{"timestamp":" 946875375183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875376453","data":{"timestamp":" 946875376452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULICHOKULA"," userResponse":" ULICHOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875378173","data":{"timestamp":" 946875378172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKAYAFANYA"," userResponse":" KIKAYAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875378752","data":{"timestamp":" 946875378752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875379754","data":{"timestamp":" 946875379754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YABUBUJIKE"," userResponse":" YABUBUJIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875382991","data":{"timestamp":" 946875382991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875385112","data":{"timestamp":" 946875385112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875387193","data":{"timestamp":" 946875387193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875389075","data":{"timestamp":" 946875389075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875390760","data":{"timestamp":" 946875390760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875392843","data":{"timestamp":" 946875392843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULICHOKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875395077","data":{"timestamp":" 946875395077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKAYAFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875397056","data":{"timestamp":" 946875397056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875399274","data":{"timestamp":" 946875399273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" heee rafiki yangu kitamu kipi ulichokula kikayafanya macho yabubujike?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YABUBUJIKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875401707","data":{"timestamp":" 946875401706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875402303","data":{"timestamp":" 946875402303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875402486","data":{"timestamp":" 946875402486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875403039","data":{"timestamp":" 946875403038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875404065","data":{"timestamp":" 946875404064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHINDWA"," userResponse":" AKASHINDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875404800","data":{"timestamp":" 946875404799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIBU"," userResponse":" KUJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875407552","data":{"timestamp":" 946875407552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875409164","data":{"timestamp":" 946875409164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875411084","data":{"timestamp":" 946875411084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875413185","data":{"timestamp":" 946875413185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875415375","data":{"timestamp":" 946875415375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHINDWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875417414","data":{"timestamp":" 946875417414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini panya wa nyumba akashindwa kujibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875419632","data":{"timestamp":" 946875419630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875419784","data":{"timestamp":" 946875419783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875420296","data":{"timestamp":" 946875420296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875421517","data":{"timestamp":" 946875421517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875422526","data":{"timestamp":" 946875422525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKEJELI"," userResponse":" AKIKEJELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875423725","data":{"timestamp":" 946875423725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" DU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875427557","data":{"timestamp":" 946875427557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875429366","data":{"timestamp":" 946875429366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875431638","data":{"timestamp":" 946875431638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875434353","data":{"timestamp":" 946875434353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875436511","data":{"timestamp":" 946875436511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKEJELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875438259","data":{"timestamp":" 946875438258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875440310","data":{"timestamp":" 946875440310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKULA"," userResponse":" UMEKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875441016","data":{"timestamp":" 946875441015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875441570","data":{"timestamp":" 946875441569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" KIASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875442769","data":{"timestamp":" 946875442768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIVIWEZI"," userResponse":" SIVIWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875443503","data":{"timestamp":" 946875443502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875444171","data":{"timestamp":" 946875444171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875446015","data":{"timestamp":" 946875446015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOHIMIDI"," userResponse":" UNAVYOHIMIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875448655","data":{"timestamp":" 946875448655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875450346","data":{"timestamp":" 946875450346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875452403","data":{"timestamp":" 946875452403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875455587","data":{"timestamp":" 946875455587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIVIWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875457350","data":{"timestamp":" 946875457350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875459458","data":{"timestamp":" 946875459457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875461735","data":{"timestamp":" 946875461734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Umekula vizuri kiasi siviwezi vitamu hivyo unavyohimidi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVYOHIMIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875465318","data":{"timestamp":" 946875465317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" KUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875466065","data":{"timestamp":" 946875466065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875466749","data":{"timestamp":" 946875466748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNAKO"," userResponse":" KUNAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875467587","data":{"timestamp":" 946875467586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKAA"," userResponse":" CHAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875468549","data":{"timestamp":" 946875468549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRADI"," userResponse":" MRADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875469299","data":{"timestamp":" 946875469297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKO"," userResponse":" KWAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875469923","data":{"timestamp":" 946875469923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875470412","data":{"timestamp":" 946875470412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BORA"," userResponse":" BORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875471141","data":{"timestamp":" 946875471140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875471850","data":{"timestamp":" 946875471850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" KUWEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875472571","data":{"timestamp":" 946875472571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875473304","data":{"timestamp":" 946875473304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZURI"," userResponse":" KUZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875474027","data":{"timestamp":" 946875474026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875475462","data":{"timestamp":" 946875475462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGALAU"," userResponse":" ANGALAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875475660","data":{"timestamp":" 946875475660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875476143","data":{"timestamp":" 946875476142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875476344","data":{"timestamp":" 946875476344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875477158","data":{"timestamp":" 946875477158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875477669","data":{"timestamp":" 946875477668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875480150","data":{"timestamp":" 946875480150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875482241","data":{"timestamp":" 946875482241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875484230","data":{"timestamp":" 946875484230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875486101","data":{"timestamp":" 946875486100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875488049","data":{"timestamp":" 946875488049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875490064","data":{"timestamp":" 946875490064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875492160","data":{"timestamp":" 946875492160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875493808","data":{"timestamp":" 946875493808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BORA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875495538","data":{"timestamp":" 946875495538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875497445","data":{"timestamp":" 946875497445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875499532","data":{"timestamp":" 946875499532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875501529","data":{"timestamp":" 946875501529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875503101","data":{"timestamp":" 946875503101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875505737","data":{"timestamp":" 946875505737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGALAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875507341","data":{"timestamp":" 946875507341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875509263","data":{"timestamp":" 946875509263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875510953","data":{"timestamp":" 946875510953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875513156","data":{"timestamp":" 946875513155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875514873","data":{"timestamp":" 946875514873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875516885","data":{"timestamp":" 946875516885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875517040","data":{"timestamp":" 946875517040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 4dcf3eca-dfde-4123-be84-07f4db11e471"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875526595","data":{"timestamp":" 946875526595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875526826","data":{"timestamp":" 946875526826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875527798","data":{"timestamp":" 946875527798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875529080","data":{"timestamp":" 946875529079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875532010","data":{"timestamp":" 946875532010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875532854","data":{"timestamp":" 946875532854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875533167","data":{"timestamp":" 946875533167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875534400","data":{"timestamp":" 946875534400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875537870","data":{"timestamp":" 946875537870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875538853","data":{"timestamp":" 946875538853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875539106","data":{"timestamp":" 946875539106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875540048","data":{"timestamp":" 946875540047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875542863","data":{"timestamp":" 946875542863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875543903","data":{"timestamp":" 946875543903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875544384","data":{"timestamp":" 946875544383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875548892","data":{"timestamp":" 946875548891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875549002","data":{"timestamp":" 946875549001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875557025","data":{"timestamp":" 946875557025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 27a63274-ba56-4d1f-8799-8f562515d499"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875569992","data":{"timestamp":" 946875569992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875576647","data":{"timestamp":" 946875576647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875586845","data":{"timestamp":" 946875586845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875596894","data":{"timestamp":" 946875596894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875602860","data":{"timestamp":" 946875602860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875609093","data":{"timestamp":" 946875609093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875614617","data":{"timestamp":" 946875614617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875625008","data":{"timestamp":" 946875625008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875631486","data":{"timestamp":" 946875631486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875661534","data":{"timestamp":" 946875661534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875671104","data":{"timestamp":" 946875671104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875680551","data":{"timestamp":" 946875680551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875687826","data":{"timestamp":" 946875687826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875698838","data":{"timestamp":" 946875698838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875707984","data":{"timestamp":" 946875707984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875714332","data":{"timestamp":" 946875714331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875723560","data":{"timestamp":" 946875723559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 7ebce309-b945-4cac-ba02-a4245d4a4f2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875738720","data":{"timestamp":" 946875738720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875745168","data":{"timestamp":" 946875745167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pabihako_lazububu-pabihako-kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pabihako"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875754897","data":{"timestamp":" 946875754897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pabihako_lazububu-pabihako-kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pabihako"," userResponse":" pabihako"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875761674","data":{"timestamp":" 946875761674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dovimahu_heyiyiku-velohuha-dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dovimahu"," userResponse":" dovimahu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875767489","data":{"timestamp":" 946875767489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zazumuba"," userResponse":" zazumuba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875776272","data":{"timestamp":" 946875776272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fizevana_fizevana-honojuye-tetafeki"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fizevana"," userResponse":" fizevana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875784019","data":{"timestamp":" 946875784018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jimidelo_zatuteme-burigema-jimidelo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jimidelo"," userResponse":" jimidelo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875796698","data":{"timestamp":" 946875796697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosihife"," userResponse":" kosihife"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875804787","data":{"timestamp":" 946875804787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavunahe_kavunahe-timumugu-pukamebu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavunahe"," userResponse":" kavunahe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875811512","data":{"timestamp":" 946875811512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasavefi_burigema-hasavefi-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasavefi"," userResponse":" hasavefi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875818173","data":{"timestamp":" 946875818173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" heyiyiku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875826347","data":{"timestamp":" 946875826347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wovudaku"," userResponse":" wovudaku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875832106","data":{"timestamp":" 946875832105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875837851","data":{"timestamp":" 946875837851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" e75be23b-9a74-48f4-a1da-7a7fbfe7a171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_wovudaku_wovudaku-jimidelo-heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875850207","data":{"timestamp":" 946875850206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875851369","data":{"timestamp":" 946875851369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875852252","data":{"timestamp":" 946875852252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875853325","data":{"timestamp":" 946875853325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875854330","data":{"timestamp":" 946875854329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875855182","data":{"timestamp":" 946875855182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875856275","data":{"timestamp":" 946875856275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875856928","data":{"timestamp":" 946875856928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875858212","data":{"timestamp":" 946875858212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875862586","data":{"timestamp":" 946875862586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875865537","data":{"timestamp":" 946875865537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875867583","data":{"timestamp":" 946875867583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875869522","data":{"timestamp":" 946875869522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875872802","data":{"timestamp":" 946875872801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875875109","data":{"timestamp":" 946875875109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875878356","data":{"timestamp":" 946875878355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875882942","data":{"timestamp":" 946875882942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875887483","data":{"timestamp":" 946875887483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875889444","data":{"timestamp":" 946875889444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875889634","data":{"timestamp":" 946875889633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875890609","data":{"timestamp":" 946875890608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875891972","data":{"timestamp":" 946875891972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" ULITENGEZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875892115","data":{"timestamp":" 946875892115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875893259","data":{"timestamp":" 946875893259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" SHANGAZIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875893915","data":{"timestamp":" 946875893914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875895003","data":{"timestamp":" 946875895003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875895787","data":{"timestamp":" 946875895786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875895900","data":{"timestamp":" 946875895899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875896593","data":{"timestamp":" 946875896593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" MTENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875899518","data":{"timestamp":" 946875899518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875901253","data":{"timestamp":" 946875901253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875903328","data":{"timestamp":" 946875903328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875906603","data":{"timestamp":" 946875906603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITENGEZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875908954","data":{"timestamp":" 946875908954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875910655","data":{"timestamp":" 946875910655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZIYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875912578","data":{"timestamp":" 946875912578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875914331","data":{"timestamp":" 946875914331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875916390","data":{"timestamp":" 946875916389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875920025","data":{"timestamp":" 946875920025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875922196","data":{"timestamp":" 946875922196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka wa kipekee ulitengezwa na shangaziye Akai kutoka majani ya mtende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875924562","data":{"timestamp":" 946875924561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875925441","data":{"timestamp":" 946875925438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875925677","data":{"timestamp":" 946875925677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875926303","data":{"timestamp":" 946875926301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875926420","data":{"timestamp":" 946875926420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875927426","data":{"timestamp":" 946875927425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875928332","data":{"timestamp":" 946875928332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875929027","data":{"timestamp":" 946875929027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875930290","data":{"timestamp":" 946875930290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" CHANIKIWITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875933383","data":{"timestamp":" 946875933383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875940568","data":{"timestamp":" 946875940567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875944750","data":{"timestamp":" 946875944750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875946725","data":{"timestamp":" 946875946725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875948420","data":{"timestamp":" 946875948420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875950596","data":{"timestamp":" 946875950596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875952515","data":{"timestamp":" 946875952514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875954391","data":{"timestamp":" 946875954391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875956842","data":{"timestamp":" 946875956842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mkeka ulikuwa wa rangi ya waridi bluu na chanikiwiti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANIKIWITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875958911","data":{"timestamp":" 946875958911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875959944","data":{"timestamp":" 946875959944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875960137","data":{"timestamp":" 946875960137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875960840","data":{"timestamp":" 946875960840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" MIKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875961833","data":{"timestamp":" 946875961833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" MINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875962817","data":{"timestamp":" 946875962817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875963551","data":{"timestamp":" 946875963551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875964135","data":{"timestamp":" 946875964135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875964979","data":{"timestamp":" 946875964979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875965482","data":{"timestamp":" 946875965482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875966316","data":{"timestamp":" 946875966316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875970626","data":{"timestamp":" 946875970626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875972944","data":{"timestamp":" 946875972944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875975369","data":{"timestamp":" 946875975369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875977487","data":{"timestamp":" 946875977487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875979451","data":{"timestamp":" 946875979451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875981487","data":{"timestamp":" 946875981487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875988121","data":{"timestamp":" 946875988121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875991544","data":{"timestamp":" 946875991544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946875998841","data":{"timestamp":" 946875998841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876000112","data":{"timestamp":" 946876000112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876001897","data":{"timestamp":" 946876001896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876002870","data":{"timestamp":" 946876002870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876005085","data":{"timestamp":" 946876005085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876007597","data":{"timestamp":" 946876007597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa tofauti na mikeka mingine ambayo mamake Akai alikuwa nayo nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876010479","data":{"timestamp":" 946876010479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876011166","data":{"timestamp":" 946876011165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876011969","data":{"timestamp":" 946876011968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876013129","data":{"timestamp":" 946876013128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876013793","data":{"timestamp":" 946876013792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876014454","data":{"timestamp":" 946876014454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876015165","data":{"timestamp":" 946876015164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876016092","data":{"timestamp":" 946876016091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876016983","data":{"timestamp":" 946876016983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876017228","data":{"timestamp":" 946876017228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876018524","data":{"timestamp":" 946876018524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ILIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876019114","data":{"timestamp":" 946876019114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" MAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876020704","data":{"timestamp":" 946876020704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876021064","data":{"timestamp":" 946876021064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876023272","data":{"timestamp":" 946876023271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876025677","data":{"timestamp":" 946876025677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876026695","data":{"timestamp":" 946876026695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876028456","data":{"timestamp":" 946876028454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876029842","data":{"timestamp":" 946876029842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876033184","data":{"timestamp":" 946876033183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876034974","data":{"timestamp":" 946876034973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876036679","data":{"timestamp":" 946876036678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876041774","data":{"timestamp":" 946876041774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876044359","data":{"timestamp":" 946876044358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876046374","data":{"timestamp":" 946876046374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876048782","data":{"timestamp":" 946876048782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876050360","data":{"timestamp":" 946876050360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumbani kwao Akai ilikuwa katika sehemu kavu yenye joto na iliyojaa mawe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876052368","data":{"timestamp":" 946876052368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876052701","data":{"timestamp":" 946876052701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876053434","data":{"timestamp":" 946876053434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" NGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876055077","data":{"timestamp":" 946876055077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876055561","data":{"timestamp":" 946876055560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876056078","data":{"timestamp":" 946876056077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876056577","data":{"timestamp":" 946876056576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876059340","data":{"timestamp":" 946876059340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876063028","data":{"timestamp":" 946876063027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876067490","data":{"timestamp":" 946876067489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876073093","data":{"timestamp":" 946876073093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876079027","data":{"timestamp":" 946876079026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876081260","data":{"timestamp":" 946876081259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876083688","data":{"timestamp":" 946876083687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kulikuwa na nge buibui na nyoka pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876086239","data":{"timestamp":" 946876086239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876086907","data":{"timestamp":" 946876086907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876088363","data":{"timestamp":" 946876088362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" HAKUWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876088977","data":{"timestamp":" 946876088977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" UMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876089561","data":{"timestamp":" 946876089560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876090249","data":{"timestamp":" 946876090248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876090676","data":{"timestamp":" 946876090675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876091684","data":{"timestamp":" 946876091684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876094963","data":{"timestamp":" 946876094963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876098125","data":{"timestamp":" 946876098124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876100574","data":{"timestamp":" 946876100574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876102704","data":{"timestamp":" 946876102704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876104814","data":{"timestamp":" 946876104814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876107054","data":{"timestamp":" 946876107054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876116588","data":{"timestamp":" 946876116588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876120546","data":{"timestamp":" 946876120546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Akai hakuwahi umwa na viumbe hao hatari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876122975","data":{"timestamp":" 946876122975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876123958","data":{"timestamp":" 946876123958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876124954","data":{"timestamp":" 946876124954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876125467","data":{"timestamp":" 946876125467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876125640","data":{"timestamp":" 946876125639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876126889","data":{"timestamp":" 946876126888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" KIPEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876128292","data":{"timestamp":" 946876128292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" UNAMKINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876128536","data":{"timestamp":" 946876128535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876129673","data":{"timestamp":" 946876129672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" HATARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876130258","data":{"timestamp":" 946876130257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" YOYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876133140","data":{"timestamp":" 946876133140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876135226","data":{"timestamp":" 946876135226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876138381","data":{"timestamp":" 946876138381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876141227","data":{"timestamp":" 946876141227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876143568","data":{"timestamp":" 946876143568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876145959","data":{"timestamp":" 946876145959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEKEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876160252","data":{"timestamp":" 946876160251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAMKINGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876162400","data":{"timestamp":" 946876162400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876164571","data":{"timestamp":" 946876164571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876166959","data":{"timestamp":" 946876166959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alisema Mkeka wake wa kipekee unamkinga na hatari yoyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOYOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876169510","data":{"timestamp":" 946876169509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876169867","data":{"timestamp":" 946876169867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876170311","data":{"timestamp":" 946876170310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876170499","data":{"timestamp":" 946876170498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876170632","data":{"timestamp":" 946876170632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NYANYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876171489","data":{"timestamp":" 946876171488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876176410","data":{"timestamp":" 946876176410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876183402","data":{"timestamp":" 946876183402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876185666","data":{"timestamp":" 946876185665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" START_MANYATTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876186629","data":{"timestamp":" 946876186629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYATTA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876188718","data":{"timestamp":" 946876188718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876190670","data":{"timestamp":" 946876190669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876193244","data":{"timestamp":" 946876193244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua mahali manyatta ya nyanyake ilikuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876194390","data":{"timestamp":" 946876194390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MANYATTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876194956","data":{"timestamp":" 946876194956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876195212","data":{"timestamp":" 946876195211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876195889","data":{"timestamp":" 946876195888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876196111","data":{"timestamp":" 946876196110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876196145","data":{"timestamp":" 946876196145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876196788","data":{"timestamp":" 946876196788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876197228","data":{"timestamp":" 946876197227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876197761","data":{"timestamp":" 946876197761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876197806","data":{"timestamp":" 946876197806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876197999","data":{"timestamp":" 946876197999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876198441","data":{"timestamp":" 946876198439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876218628","data":{"timestamp":" 946876218628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876218711","data":{"timestamp":" 946876218710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYAKE"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876226655","data":{"timestamp":" 946876226655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876234325","data":{"timestamp":" 946876234324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876243392","data":{"timestamp":" 946876243392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" f732d742-794f-4943-b6d0-5c35ad3e4334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mara kwa mara alienda kufurahia kunywa maziwa ya ngamia na nyanyake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876264906","data":{"timestamp":" 946876264906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876271558","data":{"timestamp":" 946876271558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876278182","data":{"timestamp":" 946876278182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876285658","data":{"timestamp":" 946876285658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876292300","data":{"timestamp":" 946876292299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876298974","data":{"timestamp":" 946876298973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876305603","data":{"timestamp":" 946876305602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876313139","data":{"timestamp":" 946876313139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876319771","data":{"timestamp":" 946876319771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876326397","data":{"timestamp":" 946876326396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876333859","data":{"timestamp":" 946876333859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876344844","data":{"timestamp":" 946876344844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876351064","data":{"timestamp":" 946876351064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876357744","data":{"timestamp":" 946876357744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876365245","data":{"timestamp":" 946876365244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876376348","data":{"timestamp":" 946876376348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876384939","data":{"timestamp":" 946876384938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876391211","data":{"timestamp":" 946876391211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 638736dc-4fa1-472b-a952-6ca1906c4a33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876413349","data":{"timestamp":" 946876413349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876419942","data":{"timestamp":" 946876419942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876426551","data":{"timestamp":" 946876426551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876433997","data":{"timestamp":" 946876433997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876440639","data":{"timestamp":" 946876440639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876448049","data":{"timestamp":" 946876448049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876451018","data":{"timestamp":" 946876451018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876458725","data":{"timestamp":" 946876458725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876468861","data":{"timestamp":" 946876468860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 9620d148-3dcc-43f7-af8b-ed79de8c0791"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876478086","data":{"timestamp":" 946876478086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876478309","data":{"timestamp":" 946876478309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876479272","data":{"timestamp":" 946876479272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876480553","data":{"timestamp":" 946876480552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876483407","data":{"timestamp":" 946876483406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876484249","data":{"timestamp":" 946876484248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876484575","data":{"timestamp":" 946876484575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876485825","data":{"timestamp":" 946876485825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876489376","data":{"timestamp":" 946876489376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876490369","data":{"timestamp":" 946876490368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876490624","data":{"timestamp":" 946876490624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876491578","data":{"timestamp":" 946876491578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876494555","data":{"timestamp":" 946876494554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876495602","data":{"timestamp":" 946876495601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876496086","data":{"timestamp":" 946876496085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876500649","data":{"timestamp":" 946876500649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876500719","data":{"timestamp":" 946876500719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 060a6afb-3051-4662-bb10-5e72080f394e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876522414","data":{"timestamp":" 946876522414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876529071","data":{"timestamp":" 946876529071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876535707","data":{"timestamp":" 946876535707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876542391","data":{"timestamp":" 946876542390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876549873","data":{"timestamp":" 946876549873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876556533","data":{"timestamp":" 946876556532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876563216","data":{"timestamp":" 946876563216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876569868","data":{"timestamp":" 946876569868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876576481","data":{"timestamp":" 946876576481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876583908","data":{"timestamp":" 946876583908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876594793","data":{"timestamp":" 946876594792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876601409","data":{"timestamp":" 946876601409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876608028","data":{"timestamp":" 946876608028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876621104","data":{"timestamp":" 946876621103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876656478","data":{"timestamp":" 946876656477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" db1863fe-5f21-4adf-8b08-8eb27210398e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876678173","data":{"timestamp":" 946876678172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876684781","data":{"timestamp":" 946876684781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876691441","data":{"timestamp":" 946876691441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876698112","data":{"timestamp":" 946876698112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876705570","data":{"timestamp":" 946876705570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876711498","data":{"timestamp":" 946876711498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876717963","data":{"timestamp":" 946876717963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" efc77759-758c-43df-9f4d-d991228bee83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876740553","data":{"timestamp":" 946876740553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876747212","data":{"timestamp":" 946876747212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876753870","data":{"timestamp":" 946876753869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876760529","data":{"timestamp":" 946876760528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876767209","data":{"timestamp":" 946876767209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876773885","data":{"timestamp":" 946876773885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876780542","data":{"timestamp":" 946876780541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876787191","data":{"timestamp":" 946876787191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876794703","data":{"timestamp":" 946876794703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876801361","data":{"timestamp":" 946876801361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876808850","data":{"timestamp":" 946876808850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876817740","data":{"timestamp":" 946876817739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876824526","data":{"timestamp":" 946876824526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 60eea29c-3490-420d-9838-6eccfa5733b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876845668","data":{"timestamp":" 946876845667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yeduyamo_jigogiki_dovimahu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876852288","data":{"timestamp":" 946876852288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kosihife_pukamebu_zalokiye"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876858942","data":{"timestamp":" 946876858942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_kirarijo_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876865564","data":{"timestamp":" 946876865564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_dovimahu_zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876872260","data":{"timestamp":" 946876872259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kavunahe_mehayehe_kirarijo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876878947","data":{"timestamp":" 946876878946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tujubiri_burigema_neruzugi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876885593","data":{"timestamp":" 946876885593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nijujuwa_fizevana_lozeyimu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876892233","data":{"timestamp":" 946876892232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fopozife_jigogiki_velohuha"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876898925","data":{"timestamp":" 946876898925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zazumuba_tetafeki_royuwika"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876905593","data":{"timestamp":" 946876905593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876913069","data":{"timestamp":" 946876913069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.8.noShow.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876926121","data":{"timestamp":" 946876926120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876931548","data":{"timestamp":" 946876931548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" dc868e80-6536-4c80-925f-b0cb7b60912b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.8.noShow.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fizevana_royuwika_hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876944899","data":{"timestamp":" 946876944899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876945892","data":{"timestamp":" 946876945892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876946075","data":{"timestamp":" 946876946075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876946708","data":{"timestamp":" 946876946708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876947262","data":{"timestamp":" 946876947262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876947735","data":{"timestamp":" 946876947735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876948149","data":{"timestamp":" 946876948149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876948594","data":{"timestamp":" 946876948594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876948767","data":{"timestamp":" 946876948767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876949341","data":{"timestamp":" 946876949341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876949815","data":{"timestamp":" 946876949815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876955737","data":{"timestamp":" 946876955737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876958280","data":{"timestamp":" 946876958280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876960246","data":{"timestamp":" 946876960245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876962737","data":{"timestamp":" 946876962737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876965267","data":{"timestamp":" 946876965267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876967325","data":{"timestamp":" 946876967325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876969514","data":{"timestamp":" 946876969514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876971547","data":{"timestamp":" 946876971547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876973531","data":{"timestamp":" 946876973530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876975777","data":{"timestamp":" 946876975776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876977879","data":{"timestamp":" 946876977879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876979911","data":{"timestamp":" 946876979911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876980484","data":{"timestamp":" 946876980483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876981022","data":{"timestamp":" 946876981022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" SHAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876981240","data":{"timestamp":" 946876981240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876981634","data":{"timestamp":" 946876981633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876982421","data":{"timestamp":" 946876982421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876986066","data":{"timestamp":" 946876986065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876988835","data":{"timestamp":" 946876988835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876990958","data":{"timestamp":" 946876990958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876992981","data":{"timestamp":" 946876992980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876995730","data":{"timestamp":" 946876995730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876998292","data":{"timestamp":" 946876998292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliishi katika shamba la mtu tajiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946876999870","data":{"timestamp":" 946876999870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877000319","data":{"timestamp":" 946877000319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877000520","data":{"timestamp":" 946877000520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877001277","data":{"timestamp":" 946877001276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877002136","data":{"timestamp":" 946877002136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877002597","data":{"timestamp":" 946877002597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877002766","data":{"timestamp":" 946877002766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877003394","data":{"timestamp":" 946877003393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" SAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877003508","data":{"timestamp":" 946877003508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877004048","data":{"timestamp":" 946877004048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877005425","data":{"timestamp":" 946877005425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877008312","data":{"timestamp":" 946877008312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877010104","data":{"timestamp":" 946877010104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877011790","data":{"timestamp":" 946877011789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877013911","data":{"timestamp":" 946877013911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877016190","data":{"timestamp":" 946877016190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877018068","data":{"timestamp":" 946877018068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877019791","data":{"timestamp":" 946877019791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877022344","data":{"timestamp":" 946877022344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877026258","data":{"timestamp":" 946877026258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877028550","data":{"timestamp":" 946877028550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877031723","data":{"timestamp":" 946877031723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyumba yao ya nyasi ilikuwa mwisho wa safu ya miti iliyopendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPENDEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877034226","data":{"timestamp":" 946877034225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877035089","data":{"timestamp":" 946877035089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877035324","data":{"timestamp":" 946877035324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877035808","data":{"timestamp":" 946877035808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877035972","data":{"timestamp":" 946877035972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877036516","data":{"timestamp":" 946877036516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877037269","data":{"timestamp":" 946877037269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" MITATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877038674","data":{"timestamp":" 946877038674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" ALIUGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877039168","data":{"timestamp":" 946877039168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877040172","data":{"timestamp":" 946877040172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" KUPOTEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877040756","data":{"timestamp":" 946877040756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" UWEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877040931","data":{"timestamp":" 946877040931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877041585","data":{"timestamp":" 946877041585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877044717","data":{"timestamp":" 946877044717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877047358","data":{"timestamp":" 946877047358"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877049421","data":{"timestamp":" 946877049421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877051849","data":{"timestamp":" 946877051849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877054370","data":{"timestamp":" 946877054370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877057107","data":{"timestamp":" 946877057106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877059680","data":{"timestamp":" 946877059679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877062488","data":{"timestamp":" 946877062488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIUGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877064748","data":{"timestamp":" 946877064748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877067430","data":{"timestamp":" 946877067430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOTEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877069670","data":{"timestamp":" 946877069670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWEZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877071607","data":{"timestamp":" 946877071607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877074113","data":{"timestamp":" 946877074113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877075124","data":{"timestamp":" 946877075124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877075266","data":{"timestamp":" 946877075266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877080727","data":{"timestamp":" 946877080726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" 48201235-10bf-4654-b7b6-0a1bb1e1c64c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima alipokuwa na umri wa miaka mitatu aliugua na kupoteza uwezo wa kuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877112390","data":{"timestamp":" 946877112390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877114114","data":{"timestamp":" 946877114114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877116287","data":{"timestamp":" 946877116287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877119563","data":{"timestamp":" 946877119563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877123300","data":{"timestamp":" 946877123300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877130482","data":{"timestamp":" 946877130481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877138933","data":{"timestamp":" 946877138933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877141788","data":{"timestamp":" 946877141788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877144843","data":{"timestamp":" 946877144843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877147517","data":{"timestamp":" 946877147517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877153824","data":{"timestamp":" 946877153824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877179224","data":{"timestamp":" 946877179224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877182125","data":{"timestamp":" 946877182125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877184998","data":{"timestamp":" 946877184998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877188181","data":{"timestamp":" 946877188181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877194301","data":{"timestamp":" 946877194300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877197161","data":{"timestamp":" 946877197161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877203139","data":{"timestamp":" 946877203139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877206356","data":{"timestamp":" 946877206356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877209963","data":{"timestamp":" 946877209963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877212783","data":{"timestamp":" 946877212782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877241384","data":{"timestamp":" 946877241383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877243745","data":{"timestamp":" 946877243745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877246329","data":{"timestamp":" 946877246329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877249399","data":{"timestamp":" 946877249399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877255312","data":{"timestamp":" 946877255311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877261788","data":{"timestamp":" 946877261788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877264008","data":{"timestamp":" 946877264008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877266107","data":{"timestamp":" 946877266107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877270309","data":{"timestamp":" 946877270309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877275710","data":{"timestamp":" 946877275709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877278368","data":{"timestamp":" 946877278368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877299130","data":{"timestamp":" 946877299130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877301949","data":{"timestamp":" 946877301949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877304808","data":{"timestamp":" 946877304808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877311959","data":{"timestamp":" 946877311959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877317476","data":{"timestamp":" 946877317476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877320713","data":{"timestamp":" 946877320713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877323273","data":{"timestamp":" 946877323273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877326689","data":{"timestamp":" 946877326689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877328661","data":{"timestamp":" 946877328661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877334242","data":{"timestamp":" 946877334242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877342393","data":{"timestamp":" 946877342393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877370041","data":{"timestamp":" 946877370041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877373874","data":{"timestamp":" 946877373874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877379832","data":{"timestamp":" 946877379832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877383344","data":{"timestamp":" 946877383344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877385406","data":{"timestamp":" 946877385406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877391211","data":{"timestamp":" 946877391211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877395218","data":{"timestamp":" 946877395217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877400020","data":{"timestamp":" 946877400020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877402732","data":{"timestamp":" 946877402732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877408785","data":{"timestamp":" 946877408784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877430422","data":{"timestamp":" 946877430422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877433735","data":{"timestamp":" 946877433735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877437026","data":{"timestamp":" 946877437026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877440273","data":{"timestamp":" 946877440273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877445237","data":{"timestamp":" 946877445237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877451545","data":{"timestamp":" 946877451545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877460333","data":{"timestamp":" 946877460332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877462746","data":{"timestamp":" 946877462746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877468407","data":{"timestamp":" 946877468407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877471719","data":{"timestamp":" 946877471719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877476106","data":{"timestamp":" 946877476106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877477994","data":{"timestamp":" 946877477994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877500695","data":{"timestamp":" 946877500695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877507315","data":{"timestamp":" 946877507315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877510130","data":{"timestamp":" 946877510129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877512325","data":{"timestamp":" 946877512324"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877514962","data":{"timestamp":" 946877514962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877519103","data":{"timestamp":" 946877519103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877522416","data":{"timestamp":" 946877522416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877529925","data":{"timestamp":" 946877529925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877533270","data":{"timestamp":" 946877533270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877536662","data":{"timestamp":" 946877536662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877558789","data":{"timestamp":" 946877558789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877562299","data":{"timestamp":" 946877562299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877565762","data":{"timestamp":" 946877565762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877569678","data":{"timestamp":" 946877569678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877574111","data":{"timestamp":" 946877574111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877577720","data":{"timestamp":" 946877577720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877581970","data":{"timestamp":" 946877581970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877585013","data":{"timestamp":" 946877585013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877595755","data":{"timestamp":" 946877595755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877598514","data":{"timestamp":" 946877598514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877601692","data":{"timestamp":" 946877601692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877604713","data":{"timestamp":" 946877604713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877607972","data":{"timestamp":" 946877607972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877610205","data":{"timestamp":" 946877610204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877613798","data":{"timestamp":" 946877613798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877616710","data":{"timestamp":" 946877616709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877623797","data":{"timestamp":" 946877623797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877626686","data":{"timestamp":" 946877626685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877629632","data":{"timestamp":" 946877629632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877632294","data":{"timestamp":" 946877632293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877635960","data":{"timestamp":" 946877635960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877638815","data":{"timestamp":" 946877638815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877642607","data":{"timestamp":" 946877642607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877645286","data":{"timestamp":" 946877645286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877655014","data":{"timestamp":" 946877655013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" be1e92ba-6c92-4a0d-beb0-e32d7d996742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877671306","data":{"timestamp":" 946877671306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877689333","data":{"timestamp":" 946877689333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877691566","data":{"timestamp":" 946877691566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877694372","data":{"timestamp":" 946877694372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877697590","data":{"timestamp":" 946877697590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877703015","data":{"timestamp":" 946877703015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877710793","data":{"timestamp":" 946877710793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877721801","data":{"timestamp":" 946877721801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877723734","data":{"timestamp":" 946877723734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877727504","data":{"timestamp":" 946877727503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877729079","data":{"timestamp":" 946877729079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_heyiyiku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877751879","data":{"timestamp":" 946877751879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877758258","data":{"timestamp":" 946877758258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877761776","data":{"timestamp":" 946877761776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877767735","data":{"timestamp":" 946877767735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877770915","data":{"timestamp":" 946877770915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877772993","data":{"timestamp":" 946877772993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877776463","data":{"timestamp":" 946877776462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877779048","data":{"timestamp":" 946877779048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877782367","data":{"timestamp":" 946877782366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877783696","data":{"timestamp":" 946877783696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_fizevana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877804790","data":{"timestamp":" 946877804789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877807116","data":{"timestamp":" 946877807116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877810491","data":{"timestamp":" 946877810491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877814086","data":{"timestamp":" 946877814086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877818396","data":{"timestamp":" 946877818396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877821789","data":{"timestamp":" 946877821789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877825629","data":{"timestamp":" 946877825628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877828288","data":{"timestamp":" 946877828288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nerohoye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877835190","data":{"timestamp":" 946877835190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877838322","data":{"timestamp":" 946877838322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877840998","data":{"timestamp":" 946877840997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877843868","data":{"timestamp":" 946877843868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877847577","data":{"timestamp":" 946877847577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877851709","data":{"timestamp":" 946877851709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877855285","data":{"timestamp":" 946877855285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877857736","data":{"timestamp":" 946877857736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lazububu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877866772","data":{"timestamp":" 946877866772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877869439","data":{"timestamp":" 946877869439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877873100","data":{"timestamp":" 946877873100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877878752","data":{"timestamp":" 946877878752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877883426","data":{"timestamp":" 946877883426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877887189","data":{"timestamp":" 946877887189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877890919","data":{"timestamp":" 946877890919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877894489","data":{"timestamp":" 946877894489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nijujuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877904088","data":{"timestamp":" 946877904088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877906390","data":{"timestamp":" 946877906390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877909954","data":{"timestamp":" 946877909954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877912437","data":{"timestamp":" 946877912437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877915389","data":{"timestamp":" 946877915389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877918013","data":{"timestamp":" 946877918013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877925353","data":{"timestamp":" 946877925353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877929122","data":{"timestamp":" 946877929122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877931337","data":{"timestamp":" 946877931337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_tokuviku"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877953007","data":{"timestamp":" 946877953007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877954952","data":{"timestamp":" 946877954952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877957453","data":{"timestamp":" 946877957453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877960416","data":{"timestamp":" 946877960416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877964538","data":{"timestamp":" 946877964538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877968521","data":{"timestamp":" 946877968521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877972357","data":{"timestamp":" 946877972356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877975236","data":{"timestamp":" 946877975236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wovudaku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877984958","data":{"timestamp":" 946877984958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877988328","data":{"timestamp":" 946877988328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877990287","data":{"timestamp":" 946877990286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877993436","data":{"timestamp":" 946877993436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946877998209","data":{"timestamp":" 946877998209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878001255","data":{"timestamp":" 946878001255"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878005225","data":{"timestamp":" 946878005225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878007002","data":{"timestamp":" 946878007002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_burigema"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878017513","data":{"timestamp":" 946878017513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878024301","data":{"timestamp":" 946878024301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878026990","data":{"timestamp":" 946878026990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878030509","data":{"timestamp":" 946878030509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878033254","data":{"timestamp":" 946878033254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878036518","data":{"timestamp":" 946878036518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878039791","data":{"timestamp":" 946878039791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878043807","data":{"timestamp":" 946878043807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878046728","data":{"timestamp":" 946878046728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_katepama"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878067153","data":{"timestamp":" 946878067153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878069480","data":{"timestamp":" 946878069480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878071219","data":{"timestamp":" 946878071219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878075232","data":{"timestamp":" 946878075232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878078047","data":{"timestamp":" 946878078047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878080471","data":{"timestamp":" 946878080471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878084770","data":{"timestamp":" 946878084770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878086569","data":{"timestamp":" 946878086569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946878096114","data":{"timestamp":" 946878096114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_073129"," gameId":" aba06f5b-ee78-4861-8bab-d4e28acead0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.nonwrd.len-8.lev5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_zatuteme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}